[CouponGreat.com](https://www.coupongreat.com/) > Privacy

|     |
| --- |
| **CouponGreat.com, Inc Privacy Policy** |
|  |
| We use cookies to provide you with the best experience on our website. If you continue to use the site without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to accept all cookies on the Castrol website. Blocking certain cookies can reduce the functionality of the site. Remember you can change your settings at any time by referring to the help menu on your internet browser |
| Your personal information is kept private. |
| We’ll collect only the information we need to serve you. |
| At CouponGreat.com, we will ask you to provide us with only the personal information we need to complete your transaction, to enable us to provide you with customer service, or so that you can register for special offers, benefit programs, email updates, or other services, contests, sweepstakes, or opportunities. |
| CouponGreat.com collects no personally identifying information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. We require your email address to confirm your order and to contact you regarding your purchases and shipments. We may also ask for optional interest or demographic information which will help us and our partners gain a better understanding of who we’re serving, and therefore improve our service to you. |
| CouponGreat.com collects statistical information which allows us to track the frequency of visits to our different merchants and departments. We also collect demographic information associated with visits and purchases. This information is collected for statistical purchases only, and may be shared only in the aggregate. |
| Request to delete your personal data |
| If, at any time after registering for information, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about the use of information volunteered by you, please [send us a request](https://www.coupongreat.com/contact.php) specifying your new choice. To opt out of marketing or promotional emails, please either click unsubscribe in the body of the email communication or go to [here](https://www.coupongreat.com/unsubscribe.php) to be removed. |
| We’ll store that information securely. |
| Any information you choose to provide to CouponGreat.com will be protected by a password you set and which you alone retain. And the information is stored on a secure server which is not accessible to the Internet. |
| Like most major Web sites, CouponGreat.com uses "cookies" to enable us to serve you. Cookies are an industry-standard technology which make the use of our online shopping cart possible, among other features, and our use of cookies does not infringe upon your privacy. |
| A cookie is a small data file that a Web site writes to your hard drive when you visit, which assigns you a unique ID and allows the site to save selections made and information entered during your time at the site, and to recognize you when you return. CouponGreat.com also uses cookies to determine if you have been referred to CouponGreat.com from a particular link, banner, or partner site. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you knowingly supply yourself; a cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. |
| We won’t share any information without your permission. |
| CouponGreat.com believes in your right to informed consent in the handling of your information. We will not rent or sell your personal information to any other company unless you tell us we can. If you have been referred to us by an airline partner or other partner or affiliate, we may provide them with information to help them better serve you. And we may use your information or share it with our affiliates and partners to improve our service to you and provide you with updates about items and offers which may be of special interest to you. If you have asked that we not shre your information, we may still need to provide your contact information to third parties to ensure that you do not receive any marketing messages from them. We may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties. This information is in the form of use statistics or purchase demographics, and is never connected to personal information. |
| Your Privacy Rights |
| Please keep in mind that, the foregoing policy and our best efforts notwithstanding, we cannot unconditionally guarantee that your information will never be disclosed to a third party. We may be obligated, in certain circumstances, to disclose information to the federal government in response to a warrant or official request. So by using CouponGreat.com, you do authorize us to disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Further, the foregoing policy notwithstanding, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access private communications despite every best effort made by CouponGreat.com, using industry-standard security measures, to prevent such an occurrence. |

Categories

Disclosure:: We may earn a commission when you use one of our coupons/links to make a purchase. While CouponGreat.com makes every effort to post correct information, we can make no guarantees about the accuracy of any coupons on this site. offers are subject to change without notice. Some exclusions may apply based upon merchant policies.  
Copyright ©2024, CouponGreat.com
